Wow.
Paris.
>> [music]
>> Okay, so we were supposed to fly to
Paris tonight, but
it was snowy. Snow kind of made the
plans a little difficult. Now we're just
venturing out and we're going for
dinner.
After a few calls with the airline, we
were finally able to rebook our flight
for the next [music] day. So we set off
on the adventure. We had about a 2-hour
stop in Montreal, and then [music] we
just got on our flight straight to
Paris.
Hey, how do you open this?
Oh.
I opened it.
Welcome. We're in Paris. Welcome to my
home.
So we have all of our bags here.
Got some umbrellas because it's raining.
This view.
Wow.
Paris. Next, is this the bedroom?
Yes.
Look at this bedroom.
Oh my goodness. Beautiful bed. Look at
this shower. Oh, that's cool. little
nightstand. [music]
Okay.
Next up.
Another bedroom. This is our parents'
bedroom. Oh, Mommy,
look at this beautiful
space.
Georgina.
Wow. And then in the bathroom.
Wow.
Gorge.
Okay, so we just arrived in Paris and I
am going to take a shower and then we're
going to go out and get a coffee and
walk around. Try not to go to sleep
because then I will be completely off of
the schedule. So, going to shower and
we're just going to like get out of the
house and start walking around. My
sister and I are obviously very tired.
Neither of us slept last night. I can't
sleep on a plane. My sister can't sleep
on a plane. It's how it goes. So, we're
both obviously very tired. It's like
8:00 a.m. in Toronto and I just like
essentially just pulled an all-nighter.
But, we're just going to walk around for
a bit and explore and just like try and
stay awake. We're probably going to go
for dinner or something, but just like
go and explore. I really love Paris and
it's also just like so fun to be able to
use my French even though my French is
like kind of really bad and out of
practice, but I'm excited to be here and
you know, it's a bit rainy, but it's
such a cool city and so very excited to
explore. I'm just brushing up the
eyebrows right now. I'm using the
Glossier Boy Brow. I've been using this
a lot lately and I really honestly like
it quite a lot. It fills in my eyebrows
really nicely and subtly. But yeah, I'm
going to finish up doing my makeup, get
dressed, and then we're going to head
out and go on a little adventure. I'm so
excited.
We're just adventuring out right now
into the
into the city.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Taste test. This is what we're trying.
Cafe New York, which is like over there.
Whole cafe.
It's in Paris.
It's good.
>> [music]
[bell]
>> Hello everyone. So, first monument of
the trip we're at Notre Dame.
Look at this dog.
Hello.
>> [music]
>> Going to go to bed. I will see you all
tomorrow morning.
And good night.
Good morning everyone. It is
Wednesday. [music]
And I just woke up. I'm having a little
bit of coffee. There's someone like
literally like drilling something
outside and it's so loud. It woke me up
this morning, but I had a really good
sleep last night. I slept like all
through the night and I actually feel
like normal today instead of completely
delusional and exhausted. So, that's
always a plus.
So,
yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right.
Just got back from season.
So, I'll do a little haul of the things
that I got and then we're going to go
out for the rest of the day. Okay,
lovely people. Let me give you a haul. I
got this literal beautiful jacket. It's
such a fun little like spring jacket I
feel even though it's like really cold
still in Toronto. I'm definitely going
to be able to wear this in the spring.
It's such a beautiful cut and I love it.
It's a little cropped trench. I think
[music] it's genuinely so cute. Love it.
And then the next thing I got is just
this like oversized button up which I'm
really excited about, but it's like it's
oversized, but it's like not too big and
I feel like [music] it's really cute and
I love how like the white is kind of
it's like off-white. It's not just like
stark white. Cute.
Cute and you can like obviously unbutton
it, button it up. And I love the
sleeves. They're like
longer.
So cute.
Then we are back out on the town. We
decided to go to this place for [music]
lunch. They had like mostly gluten-free
and like health food stuff, but it's
actually really good. And then we walked
around more. I love all of like the
little things that you see when you walk
out just like all of the stands with the
art, the bakeries, [music] just so many
cute little shops and everything. Just
walking around is literally the best cuz
you just get to see everything. And then
we went into Notre Dame, which was
[music] also just so so beautiful.
Walked around even more and then headed
home.
Okay, just got home. It was a very fun
day. It's currently 6:30 and now we're
just going to go get dressed to go for
dinner. We're going around like 7:00.
So, I'm going to start getting dressed
for that.
For dinner we headed to Le Recamier and
they specialized in soufflés. [music]
For dinner we got this mushroom spinach
soufflé and then the desserts were
honestly so so good. They actually had
gluten-free options so we got this one
pistachio and chocolate soufflé. So so
so good. And then the other one we got
was almond and caramel. [music]
Definitely recommend. So good. And then
we headed back and then I had a
peppermint tea when I got back.
I was up pretty late working on one of
my assignments and so now I'm finally
going to go to bed. So, I'll see you all
tomorrow morning.
So, bye.
Today
we are going to Musée de l'Orangerie.
And then I think we also want to go to
the Dior Museum. I think it's putting on
some sort of museum. Maybe I think it's
like
maybe archive fashion. Like I'm not
really sure what it is, but it seems
really cool. So, we're going to try and
get into that, but it's all sold out.
So, they sell tickets at the door so
we're going to try and get some of
those. Right now I'm just getting ready
for that. Okay, so here's the outfit
today. These shoes I got in London.
These jeans are Reformation. My bag This
and then this coat is my sister's. And
then this necklace Monica Vinader, rings
Mejuri, and these are from my mom.
I genuinely loved this art gallery. My
mom said that when she lived here in the
'90s, she would always come here and
just [music] stare at the paintings for
hours because it was just such a
peaceful environment and it was never
really that busy. And I thought that
that was really cool to experience that
again with her. And then we saw the rest
of the gallery. And I [music] just love
smaller galleries because I feel like
you can really truly appreciate all the
art that is there.
Hello everyone.
Currently back from the day. We went to
the museum the L'Orangerie.
Did a lot of walking around, had some
lunch, and now we're back. I could
probably sleep for 15 hours at this
point. Could go to bed and I wouldn't
wake up for
15 hours.
But in 45 minutes we're going to dinner.
And then after dinner we have this gala
and it's like 1920s themed, which is
like really cool. I'm very excited to go
to that. I bought a little dress for
that so that should be really fun. I
just finished a discussion post that
literally took me like 2 weeks for no
apparent reason. And I want to start
doing my makeup and getting ready for
dinner. That
is what's going on. This blanket is so
warm and I just want to sit here forever
I think.
>> [music]
>> We just got back from dinner. I've done
my makeup and done my hair. What I'm
doing for my hair is I'm doing like a
sort of like headband. I think I'm going
to do something like this.
I don't know.
Okay, so
this is the dress that I'll be wearing
tonight. It actually looked like this on
both sides, but then I
sequined the front because I was like
this shiny is a little bit chewy.
I don't know. Is it chewy to say the
word chewy? I don't know guys. But this
is the dress I'm wearing Georgina.
Okay, we're going to put this on.
Here's the dress.
>> [music]
>> Okay everyone, let's go to the party.
It's chill.
Oh,
it's chill.
Oh, there's a bike there. The shoes.
>> [music]
>> Good morning.
Didn't go to bed until like 2:00 a.m.
and had to wake up at 9:30 this morning.
Trying to wake up and
get some stuff done.
I'm actually so tired,
but I'm excited [clears throat] for the
day.
Okay, my makeup is done and now I need
to pick out an outfit which I'm a little
bit stressed about because I have no
idea what to wear. This is what I'm
wearing.
I got to go.
Okay, currently home. Did a little
outfit check. I mean did a little outfit
change. I also changed rooms because my
cousin and her boyfriend are coming to
stay with us because they live in
London, so they just took the train. So
now my sister and I share in a room.
Nice.
And
yeah, we're headed to Trocadero right
now which is like the view of the Eiffel
so we can have a view of the Eiffel
Tower. So we're going to go and do that,
which is exciting.
Afterwards, I decided that it was
[music] time to go vintage shopping. The
first place that I went was Bobby, and I
had seen a lot of like TikToks and posts
about it, so I really wanted to check it
out. [music] They had really cute stuff,
but it was a little bit more on the
expensive range. And then next, I
checked out Shay Snow Bunny, which
genuinely has such beautiful stuff, but
it was all mostly vintage [music]
designer, and so I mean the pieces were
great, but I didn't really get anything.
The next place I checked out was Aha
Vintage. There was genuinely such a
great selection, [music]
so many beautiful pieces, and it was
also a little bit more affordable than
the other two. Okay, just got back from
Eiffel Tower and then did some vintage
shopping. I went to this place called
Aha Vintage, and I got the most
beautiful jacket. Okay.
It looks literally
very similar to this one, but it's so
beautiful. It is so soft. And it's also
a lot longer.
Look at this.
She is stunning. I'm actually obsessed
with that. You hear me?
I should probably do a try-on. Like,
genuinely gorgeous. And it also has this
like this, so I can just tie it up
too, which I love. I love like that kind
of vibe as well. And it also has like
buttons as well, so I can just like
button it up, which I think is awesome.
It's also just super warm.
Stunning.
It is now time to shower and nap because
I had like 6 hours of sleep last night.
I'm actually not going to shower. I'm
simply going to wash my face and take a
nap. Time for a 1-hour nap.
Time for dinner. This is what I'm
wearing.
>> [music]
>> Good morning. I was finally able to have
like a long sleep last night. It's like
11. It's our last day in Paris. So,
yeah.
This is what I'm wearing. Just very
simple.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay. So, it is Sunday, February 1st,
and we are now heading home.
Unfortunately, it was so fun. I actually
genuinely love Paris. So, I will
be back.
>> [music]